Guide to the Hayne Family Papers1903-2015
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Photographs, Albums, and Ephemra, Series 6
  - Washington State Notebook – Jack Hayne School Notes (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Journal – Financial Book (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
  - Ledger – Financial Book (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Red Photo Album (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Research Photos #1-10 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Research Photos #11-20 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Research Photos #21-30 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Research Photos #31-40 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Research Photos #41-50 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Research Photos #51-60 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Research Photos #61-72 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Dupuyer Social Club Photos #73-75 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Political Photos #76-85 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Military Photos #86-95 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Military Photos #95-105 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Military Photos #106-115 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Military Photos #116-125 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Military Photos #126-135 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Military Photos #136-145 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Military Photos #146-152* (Box 14, Folder 16, Folder-os 1 Images 152 259)
  - Personal Photos #153-162 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Personal Photos #163-172 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Personal Photos #173-182 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Personal Photos #183-192 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Personal Photos #193-202 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Personal Photos #203-212 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Personal Photos #213-222 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Personal Photos #223-232 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Personal Photos #233-242 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Personal Photos #243-252 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Personal Photos #253-258 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Research Photos #259* (Box 16, Folder 8, Folder-os 1 Images 152 259)
  - VHS Transcript: "Grandpa Jack", Jack M. Hayne, Dupuyer, Montana Interview, November 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - A binder of extra photos from Jack Hayne's research of Montana and Dupuyer (Box 16, Item 1)
  - "Grandpa Jack", Jack M. Hayne, Dupuyer, Montana Interview, November 2000 (Box 16, Vhs 1)